Guide to the Treasurer, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Construction Records, 1752-1941; Series VI; 58; (71 boxes)
  - 1861-1921
    - Old Gymnasium; Commons 1892-1901; Herrick Hall: bids, contracts, and specifications for Commons alterations; contract for Herrick Hall alterations, 1892, 1912 (Box 448, Folder 54-55)
    - Haughton Hall: bill, 1908 (Box 448, Folder 56)
      See also: box 304, folders 1894-1895
    - Heliostat Building: contract 1915 (Box 448, Folder 57)
    - Hendrie Hall: bids, contracts, specifications, vouchers, 1894-1895 (Box 448, Folder 58-60)
    - Jane Ellen Hope Memorial Building: contracts, vouchers, bills, 1901-1904 (Box 448, Folder 61-62)
    - Jane Ellen Hope Memorial Building: specifications, 1901 May 15 (Box 449, Folder 63-65)
    - Yale Infirmary: bids, contracts, specifications, and receipts for original constructions; contract for extension, 1892-1893, 1905 (Box 449, Folder 66)
      See also: box 302, folders 1869-1870
    - Kent Chemical Laboratory; Kent Hall: vouchers for original construction; contracts, specifications, and vouchers for addition, 1887, 1901-1902 (Box 449, Folder 67)
    - Lampson Lyceum and Hall: contracts, bids, notes, specifications and vouchers, 1902-1904 (Box 449, Folder 68-69)
      See also: box 308, folder 1940
    - Lawrance Hall: contracts, bids, specifications, vouchers, account of expenditures, 1885-1886 (Box 449, Folder 70)
      See also: box 302, folder 1867
    - Linsly Hall; Linsly-Chittenden Hall: contracts, specifications, receipts, 1905-1907 (Box 450, Folder 71)
    - Marquand Chapel: contracts, 1870 (Box 450, Folder 72)
    - Medical School Building: contracts, bids, vouchers for laboratory addition, 1892-1894 (Box 450, Folder 73)
    - Osborn Memorial Laboratory: bids, contracts, vouchers, 1912-1913 (Box 450, Folder 74-77)
    - Pierson Hall: bids, contracts, specifications, vouchers, 1896 (Box 450, Folder 78)
    - Porter Gateway: contracts, 1912 (Box 450, Folder 79)
      See also: box 342, folder 2305
    - Sheffield Chemical Laboratory; Sheffield Scientific School Laboratory of Engineering Mechanics; 51 Prospect St.: bids, contracts, specifications, vouchers, 1894-1895 (Box 451, Folder 80)
    - Sloane Physics Laboratory: contracts, estimates, 1910-1912 (Box 451, Folder 81-82)
      See also: box 259, folder 1500 box 305, folders 1898-1903
    - Albert Arnold Sprague Memorial Hall: contracts, 1916-1917 (Box 451, Folder 83)
      See also: box 357, folders 2468-2470
    - Squash Courts and Bowling Alleys: contracts, 1916 (Box 451, Folder 84)
      See also: box 350, folder 2418
    - Trowbridge Library: contract, 1881 (Box 451, Folder 85)
    - Welch Hall: specifications, vouchers, 1891-1893 (Box 451, Folder 86)
      See also: box 289, folder 1759
    - West Divinity Hall; Taylor Hall: contracts, estimates, 1873-1874 (Box 451, Folder 87)
    - White Hall: contracts, estimates, vouchers, 1893-1894 (Box 451, Folder 88)
    - Winchester Hall: contracts, vouchers, 1892 (Box 451, Folder 89)
    - Winchester Observatory: contracts, 1882, 1896 (Box 451, Folder 90)
      See also: box 281, folders 1698-1699
    - Woodbridge Hall: contract, specifications, 1900 (Box 451, Folder 91)
      See also: box 322, folder 2069
    - Wright Memorial Hall: contract, vouchers, 1911-1912 (Box 451, Folder 92)
      See also: box 290, folders 1764-1768
    - Unidentified, 1917 (Box 451, Folder 93)
  - Thomas W. Farnam's Building Files
    - Yale Alumni War Memorial, 1925-1928 (Box 452, Folder 94)
      See also: box 340, folder 2251
    - Art Gallery, 1926-1931 (Box 452, Folder 95-98)
      See also: box 252, folders 1428-1434
    - Battell Chapel, alterations, 1927-1928 (Box 452, Folder 99)
    - Berkeley College, 1931-1935 (Box 453, Folder 100-102)
    - Charles W. Bingham Hall, 1926-1929 (Box 453, Folder 103-105)
      See also: box 346, folder 2364
    - Bowers Hall, 1930-1932 (Box 453, Folder 106)
    - Anthony N. Brady Memorial Laboratory, Farnam Memorial Building, and Lauder Hall, 1926-1930 (Box 453, Folder 107-110)
    - Branford College, Saybrook College, 1932-1935 (Box 454, Folder 111-113)
      See also: box 357, folder 2471
    - 65 Broadway, 1935 (Box 454, Folder 114)
    - Calhoun College, 1930-1935 (Box 454, Folder 115-120)
    - Walter Camp Gateway, 1927-1928 (Box 454, Folder 121-122)
    - Central Power Plant, 1924-1933 (Box 454, Folder 123-124)
      See also: box 265, folders 1559-1561 box 324, folders 2091-2092
    - 250 Church St., 1935 (Box 455, Folder 125)
    - 258 Church St., 1934 (Box 455, Folder 126)
    - Clinic Building (includes building conference minutes for the Medical and Pediatrics Laboratory and the Raleigh Fitkins Memorial Pavilion), 1929-1931 (Box 455, Folder 127-129)
      See also: box 458, folder 169
    - Charles E. Coxe Memorial Gymnasium, 1927-1928 (Box 455, Folder 130)
      See also: box 352, folder 2428
    - DeWitt Cuyler Field Fence, 1928 (Box 455, Folder 131)
    - Davenport College, Pierson College, 1930-1935 (Box 455, Folder 132-134)
    - Dickinson Hall
      See: box 456, folder 138
    - Dwight Hall, alterations, 1926-1932 (Box 455, Folder 135)
      See also: box 259, folders 1495-1496
    - Timothy Dwight College, 1934-1936 (Box 456, Folder 136-137)
    - Jonathan Edwards College (Dickinson Hall, Wheelock Hall), 1923-1928 (Box 456, Folder 138)
    - Jonathan Edwards College, 1931-1934 (Box 456, Folder 139-141)
      See also: box 329, folder 2127
    - 164 Fairfield Ave., Bridgeport, 1934-1935 (Box 456, Folder 142)
    - Farnam Memorial Building
      See: box 453, folders 107-110
    - Raleigh Fitkin Memorial Pavilion, 1928-1930 (Box 456, Folder 143-145)
      See also: box 455, folder 127
    - Gales Ferry Boat House, 1926 (Box 456, Folder 146)
      See also: box 313, folder 2008
    - Hall of Graduate Studies, 1930-1935 (Box 456, Folder 147-150)
    - 105 Grove St.
      See: box 463, folder 230, 231
    - Briton Hadden Memorial Building, 1931-1932 (Box 456, Folder 151)
    - William L. Harkness Hall, 1926-1929 (Box 457, Folder 152-153)
      See also: box 365, folders 2532-2534
    - Department of University Health Building, 1929-1931 (Box 457, Folder 154-156)
    - 47 Hillhouse Ave., alterations, 1924 (Box 457, Folder 157)
    - Institute of Human Relations (including financial analyses for Medical and Pediatrics Laboratory), 1929-1932 (Box 457, Folder 158-161)
    - Kingsley/Havemeyer House
    - Lapham Field House, 1923-1924 (Box 457, Folder 162)
      See also: box 360, folders 2495-2496
    - Lauder Hall
    - Linsly-Chittenden Hall, alterations, 1930-1932 (Box 457, Folder 163)
    - Edwin McClellan Hall, 1924-1926 (Box 457, Folder 164)
      See also: box 329, folder 2126
    - 279 Mansfield St, 1928, 1930 (Box 458, Folder 165)
    - Marsh Botanical Garden Fountain, 1928 (Box 458, Folder 166)
    - Medical and Pediatrics Laboratory (including financial analyses for Clinic Building), 1927, 1929-1931 (Box 458, Folder 167-169)
      See also: box 455, folder 127 box 457, folder 161
    - University Operations Building, 1927-1929 (Box 458, Folder 170)
      See also: box 300, folder 1846
    - Peabody Museum of Natural History, 1922-1926 (Box 458, Folder 171-172)
      See also: box 351, folders 2421-2425
    - Pierson College
      See: box 455, folders 132-134
    - Pierson-Sage Boiler and Refrigeration Plant, 1921-1922, 1929-1932 (Box 458, Folder 173)
      See also: box 265, folders 1559-1561
    - Sage Hall, 1923-1925 (Box 458, Folder 174)
      See also: box 256, folder 1470-1472
    - Saybrook College
      See: box 454, folders 111-113
    - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall, 1928-1933 (Box 458, Folder 175-178)
    - Silliman College, 1931-1932, 1939-1941 (Box 459, Folder 179-182)
      See also: box 463, folders 227-228
    - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, 1921-1926 (Box 459, Folder 183)
      See also: box 366, folder 2536
    - Sterling Divinity Quadrangle, 1930-1934 (Box 459, Folder 184-187)
    - Sterling Dormitory, 1929-1931 (Box 460, Folder 188)
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine, 1922-1925 (Box 460, Folder 189-192)
      See also: box 352, folder 2430
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine, extension, 1930-1932 (Box 460, Folder 193-195)
    - Sterling Hall of Medicine, library extension, 1939-1941 (Box 461, Folder 196-197)
    - Sterling Law Building, 1927-1933 (Box 461, Folder 198-201)
    - Sterling Memorial Library, 1922-1923, 1927-1933 (Box 461, Folder 202-205)
    - Sterling Memorial Library, 1928-1935 (Box 462, Folder 206-207)
      See also: box 368, folders 2544-2545
    - Sterling Power Plant, 1923 (Box 462, Folder 208)
    - Sterling Power Plant, addition, 1929-1933 (Box 462, Folder 209)
    - Sterling Properties, Connecticut and New York (Box 462, Folder 210)
    - University Theatre, 1925-1929 (Box 462, Folder 211-212)
      See also: box 312, folders 1982-1983
    - Ray Tompkins House, 1931-1934 (Box 462, Folder 213-217)
    - Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial Pavilion, 1931-1934 (Box 463, Folder 218-221)
    - Trowbridge Library, extension, 1925-1926 (Box 463, Folder 222)
    - Trumbull College, 1929-1935 (Box 463, Folder 223-226)
    - Vanderbilt-Scientific Halls, 1939 (Box 463, Folder 227-228)
    - Weir Hall, alterations, 1924-1925 (Box 463, Folder 229)
    - Wheelock Hall
    - 31 Whitney Ave., 1934 (Box 463, Folder 230)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1929-1934 (Box 463, Folder 231-232)
    - Payne Whitney Gymnasium, 1929-1935 (Box 464, Folder 233-237)
    - William Wirt Winchester Hospital, West Haven, laundry extension, 1930 (Box 464, Folder 238)
    - Winchester Observatory, alterations, 1928, 1930 (Box 464, Folder 239)
    - Woolsey Hall, refurbishing, 1922, 1928-1931 (Box 464, Folder 240)
    - Building cost estimates submitted by S. H. Francis and others, 1925-1941 (Box 464, Folder 241-242)
    - Construction personnel census, 1931-1941 (Box 464, Folder 243)
    - List of bidders approved for sub-contract work, undated (Box 464, Folder 244)
    - Time schedules with monthly progress charts, arranged chronologically, 1926 July-1933 June (Box 465, Folder 245-248)
    - Time schedules with monthly progress charts, arranged by building:, Circa 1929-1933
      - Berkeley College; Branford College and Saybrook College; Calhoun College (Box 465, Folder 249)
      - Clinic Building; Davenport College and Pierson College; Timothy Dwight College; Jonathan Edwards College (Box 465, Folder 250)
      - Hall of Graduate Studies; Department of University Health; Institute of Human Relation; Linsly-Chittenden Hall (Box 465, Folder 251)
      - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall; Silliman College; Sterling Divinity Quadrangle (Box 466, Folder 252)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine, extension and library; Ray Tompkins House (Box 466, Folder 253)
      - Sarah Way Tompkins Memorial Pavilion; Trumbull College; Payne Whitney Gymnasium (Box 466, Folder 254)
    - Bills
      - Yale Alumni War Memorial and Ledyard Flag Pole (Box 467)
      - Art Gallery (Box 467)
      - Art Gallery (Box 468)
      - Battell Chapel, alterations (Box 468)
      - Berkeley College (Box 468)
      - Berkeley College (Box 469)
      - Berkeley College (Box 470)
      - Charles W. Bingham Hall (Box 470)
      - Charles W. Bingham Hall (Box 471)
      - Bowers Hall (Box 471)
      - Anthony N. Brady Memorial Laboratory, Farnam Memorial Building, and Lauder Hall (Box 472)
      - Branford College, Saybrook College (Box 473)
      - Branford College, Saybrook College (Box 474)
      - 65 Broadway (Box 474)
      - Calhoun College (Box 475)
      - Calhoun College (Box 476)
      - Walter Camp Gateway (Box 477)
      - Central Power Plant (Box 477)
        See also: box 511 box 455, folder 125 box 455, folder 126 box 478
      - Clinic Building (Box 478)
      - DeWitt Cuyler Field Fence (Box 479)
      - Davenport College, Pierson College (Box 479)
      - Davenport College, Pierson College (Box 480)
      - Davenport College, Pierson College (Box 481)
      - Dwight Hall, alteration (Box 482)
      - Timothy Dwight College (Box 482)
      - Timothy Dwight College (Box 483)
      - Jonathan Edwards College (Dickinson Hall, Wheelock Hall) (Box 483)
      - Jonathan Edwards College (Box 484)
      - Jonathan Edwards College (Box 485)
      - Raleigh Fitkin Memorial Pavilion (Box 486)
      - Hall of Graduate Studies (Box 486)
      - Hall of Graduate Studies (Box 487)
      - Hall of Graduates Studies (Box 488)
      - 105 Grove St. (Box 488)
      - Briton Hadden Memorial Building (Box 488)
      - William L. Harkness Hall (Box 488)
      - William L. Harkness Hall (Box 489)
      - Department of University Health Building (Box 489)
      - Institute of Human Relations (Box 489)
      - Institute of Human Relations (Box 490)
      - Lapham Field House (Box 490)
      - Linsly-Chittendon Hall, alterations (Box 490)
      - 279 Mansfield St. (Box 490)
      - Marsh Botanical Garden Fountain (Box 490)
      - Medical and Pediatrics Laboratory (Box 490)
      - New Haven Hospital and Rose Street brick test panels (Box 490)
      - University Operations Building (Box 490)
      - Peabody Museum of Natural History (Box 490)
      - Pierson-Sage Boiler and Refrigeration Plant (Box 490)
      - Sage Hall (Box 490)
      - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall (Box 491)
      - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory (Box 492)
      - Sterling Divinity Quadrangle (Box 493)
      - Sterling Divinity Quadrangle (Box 494)
      - Sterling Dormitory (Box 494)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 495)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 496)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine (Box 497)
      - Sterling Hall of Medicine, extension (Box 498)
      - Sterling Law Buildings (Box 499)
      - Sterling Law Buildings (Box 500)
      - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 501)
      - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 502)
      - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 503)
      - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 504)
      - Sterling Memorial Library (Box 505)
      - Sterling Power Plant, addition (Box 505)
      - Sterling Pump House (Box 505)
      - Street Hall, alterations (Box 506)
      - University Theatre and fraternity area improvements (Box 506)
      - Ray Tompkins House (Box 507)
      - Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial Pavilion (Box 508)
      - Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial Pavilion (Box 509)
      - Trumbull College (Box 509)
      - Trumbull College (Box 510)
      - Tunnels (Box 511)
        See also: box 477
      - No. 66 Wall Street, alterations (Box 512)
      - Welch Hall, sidewalk (Box 512)
      - Payne Whitney Gymnasium (Box 512)
      - Payne Whitney Gymnasium (Box 513)
      - Payne Whitney Gymnasium (Box 514)
      - Payne Whitney Gymnasium (Box 515)
      - Winchester Observatory, alterations (Box 515)
      - Wright Hall, areaway (Box 515)
- Folio Boxes
  - Termbill charges, 1727-1732, 1755-1760, 1823 January - 1833 August (Box 108A, Folder 1-2)
  - Termbill payments: daybook, 1811 January-1820 April (Box 108A, Folder 3)
  - Ledger: dining hall, 1902-1903 (Box 108A, Folder 4)
  - Documents respecting the funds of 1792, 1792-1796 (Box 444A, Folder 5)
  - DeForest (David) Fund: terms of donation, history of fund, legal decisions, genealogy charts, Circa 1823-1907 (Box 444A, Folder 6)
  - Bergen (Francis) Memorial: deed of gift, 1919 (Box 444A, Folder 6A)
  - Trumbull (John) annuity: agreements and deed of gift for paintings, 1831-1833, 1841 (Box 444A, Folder 7)
  - Long Term Leases:, Circa 1730-1826
    - Canaan (Box 444A, Folder 8)
    - Cheshire (Box 444A, Folder 9)
    - Cornwall (Box 444A, Folder 10)
    - Goshen (Box 444A, Folder 11)
    - Kent (Box 444A, Folder 12)
    - Mansfield (Box 444A, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk (Box 444A, Folder 14)
  - Long Term Leases:, Circa 1730-1826
    - Oxford (Box 444B, Folder 15)
    - Salisbury (Box 444B, Folder 16)
    - Wallingford (Box 444B, Folder 17)
  - Securities: accrued interest ledger, 1919/1920-1921/1922 (Box 444C, Folder 18)
- Folios
  - Bills, receipts, and accounts for period recorded in ledger, "Yale College Treasury Book A", 1701-1828 (Box 58A, Folder 1)
  - Ledger style accounts of John Prout, 1756, 1759-1765 (Box 58A, Folder 2)
  - Steward's accounts, 1710, 1749-1765 (Box 58A, Folder 3-4)
- Prospectus, 1973; Accession 19ND-A-475
  - Prospectus, 1973 July 10 (Box 1)
- Reports on Yale endowment, 1973; Accession 19ND-A-492
  - Reports on Yale endowment, 1973 (Box 1)
- Records concerning the Mrs. Hepsa Eli Silliman Memorial, circa 1886-1889; Accession 1933-A-006
  - The Mrs. Hepsa Eli Silliman Memorial, circa 1886-1889 (Box 1)
- Records concerning the Yale Army Laboratory School, 1918-1920; Accession 1935-A-007
  - Yale Army Laboratory School
    - Contracts, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Room & Board statements for reimbursement, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Utility & telephone bills & correspondence, 1918-1920 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1918-1919, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Records of the Finance Committee, 1888-1896, 1924-1944; Accession 1944-A-002
  - Finance Committee, 1888-1896, 1924-1944
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1888-1896 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Statements and Memoranda, 1924-1929 (Box 1, Folder 2-6)
    - Statements and Memoranda, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder 7-11)
    - Statements and Memoranda, 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 12-17)
    - Statements and Memoranda, 1935-1938 (Box 4, Folder 18-23)
    - Statements and Memoranda, 1938-1942 (Box 5, Folder 24-27)
    - Miscellaneous Statements, 1940-1944 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Miscellaneous Charts and Graphs, 1922-1941 (Box 6)
- Records concerning Helen Hadley Hall, 1938-1946, 1949, 1956-1959; Accession 1961-A-006
  - Cora Putnam Hale Trust Final Accounting, 1938 July - 1946 September (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Indenture of Mortgage, Conn. Boola Inc. to Crocker First National Bank of San Francisco, 1949 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Indenture of Lease between Conn. Boola Inc., Landlord and R.H. Macy & Co. Inc., Tenant, 1949 November (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Financial records, 1897-1966; Accession 1986-A-077
  - Series I
    - 1906-1919
      - Yale University: Estimated Income & Expenses, 1906-1920 (Box 1, Folder 1-14)
      - Budget & Expenditure Accounts, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Preliminary Salary Budgets:, 1919-1920
        - Art School (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Department of Botany (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Department of Chemistry (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Department of Civil Engineering (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Department of Classics (Including Archeology & Sanskrit) (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Department of Education (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Department of Engineering Mechanics (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Department of English (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - School of Forestry (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Department of Geology (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Department of German (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Department of History (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Law School (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Department of Mathematics (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Department of Mechanical Engineering (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - School of Medicine (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Department of Mining & Metallurgy (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Department of Music (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Department of Philosophy (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - Department of Physics (Box 1, Folder 35)
        - Department of Physiological Chemistry & Bacteriology (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Department of Electrical Engineering (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Department of Religion (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Department of Romance (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - Semitic & Biblical Department (Box 1, Folder 40)
        - Department of Social & Political Science (Box 1, Folder 41)
        - Department of Zoology (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 1920-1921
      - Estimated Income & Expenses (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Budget & Expenditure Accounts (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
    - 1921-1922
      - Estimated Income & Expenses (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Salary Report-Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Budget & Expenditure Accounts (Box 2, Folder 49-51)
      - Details of Special Investments (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Freshman Scholarships (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Services Bureau (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Printed Revisions (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - 1922-1923
      - Estimated Income & Expenses (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Budget & Expenditure Accounts (Box 3, Folder 57-59)
      - Details of Special Investments (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Expenditures (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Salary Budgets (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - 1923-1924
      - Details of Special Investments (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: Botany to Geology (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: German to Zoology (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative, Bureau of Appointments to School of Medicine (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative, School of Law to Miscellaneous Papers (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Disbursements of Salaries (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - 1924-1925
      - Detail of Special Investments (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Budget: Salaries, Summary of (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative: Bureau of Appointments to School of Medicine (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative: School of Law to Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: Bacteriology to Geology (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: German to Zoology (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - Estimates of Income & Expenses (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Budget: Funds, General (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - 1925-1926
      - Budget: Funds, General (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: Applied Physiology & Zoology (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - Income & Expenses, Estimates of (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative, Graduate School to Law School (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative, School of Fine Arts to Service Bureau (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Budget: Salaries, Summary of (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Details of Special Investments (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - 1926-1927
      - Budget: Funds, General (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Budget Papers: Schools & Administrative (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Budget Papers: Departments of Instruction: Applied Physiology to Zoology (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Details of Special Investments (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - 1927-1928
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - 1928-1929
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - 1929-1930
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - 1930-1931
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - 1931-1932
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - 1932-1933
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - 1933-1934
      - Budget & Expenditure Accounts: Departments (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Miscellaneous Funds (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Budget Funds (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Budget & Expenditure Account of Various Departments (Box 7, Folder 99)
      - Scholarships & Loans (Box 7, Folder 100)
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses: Departments (Box 7, Folder 101)
      - Description of Funds of Yale University & Board of Trustees of Sheffield Scientific School (Box 7, Folder 102)
      - Securities (Box 7, Folder 103)
      - Investments & Securities (Box 7, Folder 104)
      - Scholarships & Loans (Box 8, Folder 105-108)
    - 1934-1935
      - Estimate of Income & Expenses: Departments (Box 8, Folder 109)